白宫西翼
west wing
不 Rachel 抱歉
No, Rachel, I'm sorry.
但访问后副总统的邀约陡增
But the VP's schedule has skyrocketed since the interview.
实际上 我并不觉得抱歉
Actually, I'm not sorry.
我不清楚自己为什么那么说  嘿 我告诉你
I'm not sure why I just said that. Boy, I'll tell you something.
那个电视访问冒了很大的险 但完全值了
That TV interview was a big gamble, but it really paid off.
瞧这个  这是什么?
Look at this.  What is it?
他们叫你"不撒谎的副总统"
They're calling you the "no-BS VP."
就他妈是这样
Damn right they are.
我是说 我说的都是谎话 但至少听起来是真的  唔嗯
I mean, I lied and everything,  but it sounded true, at least.  Uh-huh.
心情不错
Mood is good.
只要之后的六年都像今天这样 他们就会选举我们当总统
Just need six more years like today and they will vote us POTUS.
嘿 女士 记得明天您有那个"动起来趣味(长)跑"吧
Hey, ma'am, remember tomorrow you've got that Get Moving Fun Run.
您大概应该准备准备吧 您不这么认为吗?
You probably should prepare, don't you think?
就一万米  没错
It's a 10K.  Yeah.
我穿上盔甲也能跑完  好吧
I Can run that thing in a suit of armor.  Okay.
女士 我不应该和您一起去这个捐赠者的上午餐会 我们不想引起任何警惕
Ma'am, I shouldn't go with you to this donors' brunch. We don't want to set off any alarm bells.
哦 没错 知道吗? 我也不该去
Oh, yeah. You know what? Me neither.
好吧 我会独自去亲那群讨厌的亿万富翁的屁股
Okay, I'll go kiss some hateful billionaire ass on my own.
让那些捐钱的性奋一把
Give them all donor boners.
每个人都想搭上您 女士  没错
Everyone wants a piece of you, ma'am.  Yeah.
通过我  我需要和Ben谈谈 马上
Via me. I need to go talk to Ben right now.
来了(西班牙语)!  走吧
Andale!  Let's go.
国务院告密者即将作证
state depaptment
到现在为止 我们还没有得到总统的任何消息
We haven't heard anything from the president so far.
我们收到传言 说在国务院的高层有一个告密者
We've got rumors of a whistleblower high up in the State Department.
什么? 你在做什么?
What? What are you doing?
我不想让人们看到那个  哦
I don't want people to see that.  Okay.
他们应该在Ben办公室外放一个自动发药机 对吧?  是的
They should put those in a dispenser  outside Ben's office, right?  Yeah.
白宫员工正集结律师以防传票...
White House staff are lawyering up in case of subpoenas...
Ben.
Ben?  总统自己的党派内部在谈论一个潜在的挑战者
Ben?  We've got the president's own party talking of a potential challenger...
嘿 为什么总统不干脆道个歉?
Hey, why doesn't POTUS just make an apology?
我是说 我那么做了 也就只有一个星期想自杀而已
I mean, I did and I was only, like, suicidal for a week.
哈?  因为他现在一团糟 好吗?
Huh?  Because he's a mess, all right?
他的头盖骨里有一整洞的蝙蝠
He's got a cave full of bats in his skull.
我背了整个间谍案的黑锅
I took the heat for the spy.
就一点功劳也不算么?  算
Don't I get any credit for that at all?  Yeah.
所以现在我们接到了众议院司法委员会传票 理由是"不明智"
So now we've got the House Judiciary Committee subpoenaing us senseless.
此外 还有谣言到处传
And on top of that, we got a rumor going around
说党内有个挑战者
that says that there's a challenger inside the party.
什么? 谁?  我不知道
What? Who?  I don't know.
卡扎菲i的某个儿子吧 他们的民调支持率更高
One of Gaddafi's sons. They're polling better.
所以很感谢你的帮助 但你能不能停止表现得那么他妈积极?
So thank you very much for your help, but would you quit being so goddamned proactive?
为了最后的加演你会做什么? 用尊臀投一个开幕球么?  (棒球开幕仪式)
What are you going to do for an encore? Blow the opening day pitch out of your ass?
啊 那不错
Ah, that's lovely.
未来两年也会这样?
Is this what this is going to be like for the next two years?
哦 天 是的
Oh, my, yes.
我们是挂在戒备状态上了
We are at DEFCON fuck.
嘿 女士 我准备了捐献者的资料卡
Hey, ma'am, I got flash cards on the donors.
不用了 谢谢 我能搞定
No, thanks. I got it.
Peter Spiddock与枪械共眠 Sandra O'Neill讨厌石油
Peter Spiddock sleeps with his gun, Sandra O'Neill fricking hates fracking,
Sidney Purcell... 和他说话
Sidney Purcell... talking to him,
就像被卡在了一条满是死老鼠的下水道里
it's like being stuck in a sewer pipe filled with dead rats.
他有钱来烧啊 不是说捐钱给您选举是烧钱
He's got money to burn. Not that donating to your campaign is burning money.
我完全了解这是什么 今天是个政治前戏
I know what this is all about. This is a political prick tease today.
没错 而我们马上就要见到一群老二了
Yeah, and we're about to meet a bunch of pricks.
哦 挑战者 小刺头
Yeah. Challenger schmallenger.
我是说 如果这个早午餐会进展不错 我竞选活动的发射平台就能
I mean, if this brunch goes well, my campaign launchpad is going to be made
用他妈的纯金打造了
of solid fucking gold.
六年后 就会是总统女士
And then in six years, it's gonna be Ms. President.
我们会需要更大的包!
We're gonna need a bigger bag!
总统办公室里有卵巢!
Ovaries in the Oval Office!
子宫西翼!
The West Womb!
什么?
What?
什么?  你知道 就像个子宫
What?  You know, like a womb.
就像女人孕育婴儿的子宫...
Like a woman has a womb that the baby comes...
真可悲 《政客》杂志宣布Danny Chung刚上传了 他的"我在听什么"歌单到Spotify (社区音乐分享软件)
Oh, pathetic. "Politico" is announcing that Danny Chung has just uploaded his "What I'm Listening To" playlist on Spotify.
唔 我们需要做一份歌单
Hmm. We need to do a playlist.
不 我们不需要  哦 我们完全需要
No, we don't. Oh, we absolutely do.
找Dan  不用 我能帮忙弄那些歌
Get Dan.  No, I can help with the songs.
你知道 我侄女超爱Katy Perry  我刚说了 找Dan
You know, my niece loves Katy Perry. Just like I said, get Dan.
退伍军人纪念堂
veterans memorial hall
他在那  DJ Dan
there He is.  DJ Dan.
谢谢那份歌单  哦 我的荣幸
Thanks for the playlist.  Oh, my pleasure.
看来它在各年龄的Chung粉中表现(播放)得都不错
Seems like it's playing pretty well, too, with the oldies and the Young Chungers.
年轻Chung粉
The Young Chungers.
你随便想能用来做推特话题啊  哦 你喜欢这个?
It's like you think in hashtags.  Oh, you like that?
很好 也许我们能叫那些超过65岁的为"奶奶Chung"
All right, maybe we can call the over 65ers the Granny Chungs.
类似的 不 我会继续想想
Something. No, I'll keep working on that one.
哦 去  你得接那个 让她高兴
Oh, shit. You need to take that. Keep her happy.
艰巨的任务  闻到了吗? 钱
Tall order. You smell that? Money.
嘿 Dan?
Hey, Dan?
女士  你有没有听说
Ma'am.  Have you heard anything about
Danny Chung歌单的事?
this Danny Chung playlist?
事实上 我刚知道
I just caught that, actually.
也有些俏皮时髦的东西
Some smart stuff on there, too.
面向年轻人的Nas (说唱歌手Nasir bin Olu Dara Jones)
Nas for the young folks,
给退休人员的Dean Martin (歌手 成名于30年代末)
some Dean Martin for the retirees.
他就是找了个虾兵蟹将写的
He just got one of his butt droids to do it,
这就是为什么我希望你来帮我做 懂吗?
which is why I want you to do it for me, okay?
您的混音就是我的命令 (仿"您的需求就是我的命令")
Your mix is my command.
嘿 Sue 帮我搞定这个 成吗? 你对这个很拿手
Come on, Sue, help me out with this, okay? You're good at this stuff.
你年轻 你嬉 你哈
You're young, you're hip, you're hop.
Jimmy Cliff怎么样? "不速之客"? (雷鬼歌手及其72年作品)
What about Jimmy Cliff? "The Harder They Come"?
不
No.
瞧 我完全没概念 所以 不
Look, I have no idea who that is, so, no.
Elvis Costello "和平 爱和理解"? (歌手及其78年翻唱大热歌曲)
Elvis Costello, "Peace, Love and Understanding"?
什么?  不 不 还是不
What?  No, no, and no.
这些是不是都是从你的iPod里面找出来的?
Are you getting these all from your iPod?
不 我想是在云存储中  哦
No. I think it's in a cloud.  Oh.
呃 你认为Danny Chung准备好两年后大干一场了么?
You know, do you think that Danny Chung's the one who's getting ready to bust a move in two years?
哦 看总统现在的走向
Well, the way POTUS is going,
他大概迟早会卷入战争
he'll probably stumble into a war sooner or later.
Chung会再次从军 但愿他被杀掉
Chung will reenlist and hopefully get himself killed.
我不明白为什么我不能和他一样受尊重 明白吗?
I don't understand why I don't get the same respect as he does, you know?
去!  哦 那个怎么样? "尊敬"
Shit!  Oh, what about that? "Respect. "
Sue?  你知道的 那首Aretha Franklin的歌?
Sue?  You know, the Aretha Franklin song?
是的  哦 哦 哦 哦
Yes.  Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
那会很不错  嘿 Mike Mike
That would be great.  Hey, Mike. Mike.
喔!  哦 天哪
Ooh!  Oh, my God.
女公爵受伤了 女公爵受伤了 黄色警报 黄色警报
Duchess is down. Duchess is down. Yellow, yellow.
重复 女公爵受伤了 去 Rick 走 走 走!
I repeat, Duchess is down. Go, Rick. Go, go, go, go!
哦 天哪 你的脸!
Oh, God, your face!
我们需要一个医生  很糟糕吗?
We're gonna need a medic.  Is it bad?
不  是的!
No.  Yes!
您没事 女士 您没事
You're fine, ma'am. You're fine.
副总统女士 请您站在原地不动
Madam Vice President, if you'd just stand still, please.
冷静下来 Martin 这不是恐怖分子  我没事
Calm down, Martin. It's not a terrorist.  I'm fine.
封锁过道 伙计们 没什么事
Just lock up the hallway, guys. It's all fine.
封锁 封锁  女士
Lock it up. Lock it up.  Ma'am.
嗯?  这是你要做的
Yes?  Here's what you do.
好的  别动
Okay.  Don't move.
我们要把您的衣服剪下来
We're gonna have to cut your clothes off you.
哈?  我撞破过玻璃门
Huh?  I walked through a glass door before.
这就是您要做的 好吗?  你在开玩笑
This is what you do, okay?  You're kidding.
不 我很好因为我当时喝醉了
No, I was fine because I was drunk.
您会没事  哦
You're gonna be okay.  Oh.
去 捐赠者们  去告诉他们我会晚几分钟
Shit, the donors.  Just go tell them I'm gonna be a couple minutes late.
去对他们那么说 懂吗?  好的 好的
Go tell them that, okay?  Okay, okay.
好 你在... 不 Mike!  抱歉 抱歉 抱歉
All right. What are you... no! Mike!  Sorry, sorry, sorry.
哦 去!  哦 天哪!
Oh, shit!  Oh, my God!
对不起 对不起  别... 别...
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.  Don't... don't...
走另一边 Mike  好的 好的
go another way, Mike.  Okay. Okay.
女士 女士 您觉得疼吗? 您痛吗?
Ma'am, ma'am, are you hurting? Are you in pain?
呃 我不知道
Uh, I don't know.
你有镜子吗?
Do you have a mirror?
没有  是的 你有
No.  Yes, you do.
我有些舒缓疼痛的贯叶连翘  如果您想要的话
I've got some St. John's Wort for pain relief if you want it.
我不想吃药
I don't want to take medication.
是草本的 来自大自然
It's herbal. It's from the earth.
您可以吃六片 不会有什么影响
You can take six, it won't affect you.
瞧那个
Look at that.
啊! 嗷!
Ah! Ow!
呃 副总统表示歉意 但她稍微有些晚点
Uh, the vice president apologizes, but she's slightly delayed.
她正和澳大利亚大使通话  澳大利亚大使?
She's stuck on a call with the Australian ambassador. The Australian ambassador?
真不错 这一条我还没听过呢
That's good. I've never heard that one before.
Sidney Purcell 见到你总是令人愉快 先生
Sidney Purcell, always a pleasure, sir.
不 事实上不愉快  不过你这么努力有加分
No, it's not, actually, but you get marks for trying.
但副总统情绪高涨
But the vice president is in great spirits.
她迫不及待地想和你们所有人见面 我去看看 看我是否能打断那个电话
She's buoyantly waiting to meet you all and I will go check, see if I can interrupt that call.
就像我说的 是个电话
Like I said, it's a call.
退伍军人纪念堂
veterans memorial hall
力量是灵活但坚定的
Strength is being flexible and steadfast.
它是活下来的柳树 而不是枯死的橡木
The living willow, not the dead oak.
我在伊拉克懂得了 我与战友之间那条通往尊敬的路是双向的
I learned in Iraq that the road to respect between me and my men ran two ways.
为了得到尊敬 你得付出尊敬
In order to get respect, you have to give respect.
当我向外看的时候 我看到很多张脸 但我只看到了一个国家
When I look out, I see many faces, but I see only one nation
一个有统一志向的国家
with one aspiration,
那个志向就是某一天希望可以一起梦想
and that aspiration is to one day hope to dream together.
有一天 我在St. Paul  不
I met a young woman...  No.
遇到了一个叫Juanita的年轻女性
Named Juanita in St. Paul the other day.
哦 去他的  当我问... 你知道她对我说了什么吗?
Oh, crap. And I asked... You know what she said to me?
Dan  这很尴尬
Dan.  This is awkward.
就像在狂欢放荡的时候吸引了你姐妹的注意  哦 我姐妹绝不会狂欢
Like catching your sister's eye at an orgy. Well, my sister would never be at an orgy.
太紧张了
Too uptight.
她会想要每个人的健康报告 然后败兴...  好吧
She would want health records from everyone  and just kill the momentum and...  Okay.
我对你很失望  这种行为我自己有不奇怪
I'm disappointed in you. This is behavior I would expect from myself.
但是你? 不行
But from you? Uh-uh.
咱们别废话了吧 我们都是为了Chung助阵来的
Let's cut the crap. We're both here for Chung.
那我们一起跳 Butch和Sundacne(《虎豹小霸王》)  他们不是都死了吗?
So we both jump together. You know, Butch and Sundance. Don't they both die?
不 跳的时候没死 结局的时候才死的
No, not when they jump. They die at the end.
嘿 Sue  Dan 副总统刚刚撞破了一扇玻璃门
Hey, Sue. Dan, the vice president just walked through a glass door.
她撞破了一扇玻璃门? 那是什么 密码?
She walked through a glass door? What is that, code?
不 不幸的是 不是 Dan 这是对刚才发生的事的平实描述
No, unfortunately, it is not, Dan. It is a literal description of what just happened.
她伤得不是很严重 谢谢询问  她撞破了一扇玻璃门?
And she's not too badly hurt. Thanks for asking. She walked through a glass door?
是的 那女人成为了她自己事业的一个活的象征
Yeah, that woman has become a living metaphor of her own career.
确保你今天休息 好吗?
Just make sure you rest today, okay?
我觉得自己就像个被补好 送给孤儿院孩子的旧橄榄球
I feel like one of those old used footballs that they fixed up for the kids at an orphanage.
看到你冷静下来了这很好  女士 足够的休息 明天不能跑一万米
Good to see you've calmed down. Ma'am, plenty of rest and no 10K run tomorrow.
好吗?  哦 这个可不行
Okay?  Well, I don't know about that.
呃 我们告诉每个人你晚点了
Uh, we told everyone you were delayed.
但我们得取消这个 好吗?  不 Mike 你在说什么?
But we're gonna have to cancel this thing, okay? No. Mike, what are you talking about?
我不能取消我的命运  女士 看 你正穿着浴袍
I can't cancel my destiny. Ma'am, look at you. You're wearing a robe.
除非你想下去为他们唱 《看着我 我是Sandra Dee》的副歌 您不能下楼
Unless you want to go down there and sing them a chorus of "Look At Me, I'm Sandra Dee," you can't go downstairs.
好了 我先离开  非常感谢您的帮助
Okay, I'll go ahead and go. Thank you very much for your help.
保密?  哦 当然
Mum's the word?  Oh, yes.
好极了  我究竟该说什么?
Good.  What Would I even say?
我们就直接告诉他们发生了什么然后重新安排
We'll just tell them what happened and reschedule.
天哪  哦 天哪
Jesus.  Oh, God.
我去取消 我去取消
I'm cancelling. I'm cancelling.
好吧 她在哪?  我不知道
Okay, where is she?  I don't know.
我猜我们就跟着她的血迹还有Gary的泪痕
I guess we just follow the trail of her blood and Gary's tears.
哦 嘿  她有多糟糕?
Oh, hey.  How bad is she?
她没事 只是些表面割伤  你有给她吃止痛药或者...?
She's fine. It's just superficial cuts. Did you give her any painkillers or...?
你知道 我不想那么做 因为她已经吃了贯叶连翘
u konwI didn't want to do that because she's already on St. John's Wort.
我想某次我在一个天主教学校的女孩那听到过 (常用于舒缓痛经)
I think I got that off a Catholic schoolgirl once.
那么为什么她不能吃其他的药?  哦 那会对身体造成很坏的影响
So why can't she take anything else? Well, it can react badly with the body
如果她已经在服用免疫抑制剂 β-受体阻滞剂 或者抗抑郁剂
if she's already on immunosuppressants, beta-blockers, or antidepressants.
哦 哦 好吧 她没有吃其中的任何一种
Oh, okay, fine. She's not on any of those.
我得走了 稍后再和你们联系  哦 谢谢
I've really got to go. Catch you guys later. Yep, thank you.
哦 她在服用抗抑郁剂  是的
Well, she is on antidepressants.  Yep.
你先请
After you.
瞧? 你让那个看起来很容易
See? You made that look so easy.
嘿 我很抱歉这不是总统套房 女士
Hey, I'm sorry this isn't the presidential suite, ma'am.
哦 没关系 Gary
Oh, it doesn't matter, Gary.
谁占了那个总统套房?
Who has the presidential suite?
我听说是Russell Crowe
I heard Russell Crowe.
Russell Crowe "角斗士"  是的
Russell Crowe, "Gladiator. "  Yeah.
我会回来的 (这是施瓦辛格州长的名言)
I'll be back.
你知道谁会喜欢这件浴袍吗?  谁?
You know Who Would love this robe?  Who?
Ben  是的 是的 是的
Ben.  Yeah, yeah, yeah.
你能想象他穿着这个拿着他的大马克杯吗?
Can you imagine him in this with his big mug?
是的 是的  到处转悠?
Yep, yep.  Walking around?
他会喜欢的
He'd love that.
来吧 坐这  好的 您真好
Come on, sit here.  Okay, that's nice.
是的  谢谢 女士
Yeah.  Thank you, ma'am.
我真的不清楚你的任何事 你知道吗? 你是个有点神秘的男人
I don't really know anything about you, you know? You're kind of a mystery man.
你在哪长大的?
Where'd you grow up?
阿拉巴马州Birmingham  你不是
Birmingham, Alabama. You did not.
我也是! 我是!
I did too! I did!
你和你的父母很亲近吗?  和我妈妈亲近
are You close to your parents?  close to my mom.
我爸爸总是想有个男人一样的儿子 所以...
My dad always wanted a man for a son, so...
哦 是的  但时代不同了
Oh, yeah.  But it's a different generation.
时代不同了 这是事实
It is a different generation. It's true.
他们马上就要庆祝第四十个结婚纪念日了
They're about to celebrate their 40th wedding anniversary.
四-零  哦!
4-0.  Oh!
他们会有个盛大的宴会
They're gonna have a huge blowout.
你指什么? 像个派对?  超大规模的派对
What Do You mean? Like a party?  Massive party.
超大的 是的 是的 是的
Massive. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
那十分...  我能去吗?
It's really...  Can I come?
什么?  我...我能去吗?
What?  Could... Can I come?
您认真的?
Are you serious?
我不请自来很不合适吗?
Is that completely inappropriate for me to invite myself?
哦 天哪 不
Oh, my God, no.
不 他们... 我会很高兴
No. They... I would love that.
你在开玩笑吗?  真的吗?
are You kidding?  Really?
是的
Yes.
那会解决我和父亲之间所有关于有效性的问题
That would solve all of my validation issues with my dad.
女士 呃 您好吗?
Ma'am. Uh, how are you?
瞧 Amy 看这个
Look, Amy, watch this.
瞧我能把自己缩得多小 看着
Look how tiny I can make myself. Watch this.
但那个捐赠者会议被取消了 对吗?
But the donor meeting has been cancelled, yes?
我不会参加那个
I'm not doing that thing.
认真的 让那些人都去死吧
Seriously, screw all those people.
天 我希望伊朗丢颗核弹到特区
God, I hope Iran drops a nuke on DC.
喔  那不是会解决绝大部分问题吗?
Ooh.  Wouldn't that solve a lot of issues?
只是Kent肯定不会挪窝
Except Kent wouldn't go anywhere.
他仍然会在附近 他就像只不死的蟑螂 和他的...
He'd still be around. He's like an undead cockroach with his...
是事实
It's true.
他有张面瘫的脸
He's got that blank look.
我肯定他甚至没有高潮的表情 你能想象和那个男人上床吗?
I bet he doesn't even have a come face. Can you imagine fucking that guy?
Amy 你有一头非常漂亮的金发
Amy, you have such pretty blonde hair.
不是吗?
Doesn't she?
太漂亮了
So pretty.
嗨 大家好 再一次早上好
Hi, everyone. Good morning again.
不幸的是 副总统仍在和澳大利亚通话
Unfortunately, the vice president is still stuck on a phone call with Australia
所以她要将此次晨会还有问候早餐延后了 好吗? 我们非常抱歉
so she's going to have to postpone this morning's meet and greet breakfast, okay? We're very sorry.
Mike 你知道吗 在南半球 这些狗屁是朝另一个方向转的
Mike, you know, in the southern hemisphere, the bullshit actually flows the other way.
你知道吗?
Did you know that?
澳大利亚的事情是真的  哦
the Australia thing is real.  Yeah.
那他妈的的又怎样?  好吧 听我说
What the fuck?  Okay, listen to me.
副总统出了点状况
There's been an incident with the vice president.
你能保密吗?  能  什么?
Can You Keep this under wraps?  Yeah. What?
她撞破了一扇玻璃门
She's walked through a glass door.
她撞破了一扇玻璃门  嘘
She walked through a glass door?  Shh!
什么 她绊倒在了一块坚硬的玻璃上?
What, she just stumbled into a solid piece of glass?
是的
Yes.
那... 那真神奇
That's... that's amazing.
我猜它有趣是因为我们在某些时候都做过
I guess it's funny because we've all done it at one point.
我没有  我把某人推倒并撞破了平板玻璃门
I haven't. I pushed someone through a plate glass door once.
那太他妈的搞笑了  别笑了
That was fucking hilarious. Stop laughing.
她还好吗?
Is she okay?
唔 就是有些割伤
Mm. Just cuts.
你是副总统的联络人 对吧?
You are liaison to the VP, right?
That's your "liaison d'阾re"? I was born to liaise, sir.
那就是你"联络的理由 (仿法谚 存在的理由)"?  我生来就是做联络的 先生
那么为什么你不能告诉我副总统
Then why can't you tell me about what the VP was doing
撞破玻璃门的时候她在干什么?
when she walked into a glass fucking door?
好吧 呃 副总统办公室可以很不合作
Okay, well, the VP's office can be very insubordinate.
我是说 他们总是很抗拒我 你知道他们叫我Jo蛋蛋么?
I mean, they insubord me all the time. You know that they call me Jonad?
我是说 那就相当于叫总统Jo蛋蛋啊
I mean, that is tantamount to calling the president Jonad.
不 那不是 他是总统 你是Jo蛋蛋
No, it's not. He's the president, you're Jonad.
马上去那里从Sue嘴里问出事实
Now get in there and liaise the truth out of Sue
或者我会确保那名字牢牢地跟着你 直到被刻在你的墓碑上
or I'll make sure that name sticks so hard, it ends up on your gravestone.
是的 先生
Yes, sir.
你好 Susan
Hello there, Susan.
名字不是Susan 是Sue... Jo蛋蛋
Name's not Susan, it's Sue... Jonad.
够了 我的名字不是Jo蛋蛋!
Okay, and my name isn't Jonad!
是Jonah 别用这个侮辱我 Sue
It's Jonah. Do not disrespect me on this, Sue.
喔 喔 喔 这儿没有人侮辱你...
Whoa, whoa, whoa, no one here is disrespecting you...
Jo蛋蛋 去挣得你改名字的权利
Jonad. Now go earn your name change.
Sue  先生
Sue.  Sir.
副总统今天早上在酒店做什么?
What was the vice president doing at that hotel this morning?
会见并问候美国教师协会
Meet and greet with the American Teachers Association.
如果我打电话给美国教师协会 他们会证实
If I call the ATA, they would confirm
她有和他们会面并问候?  呃 没法保证
that she was meeting and greeting them? Uh, couldn't say.
如果你没法告诉我她当时在干什么
If you can't tell me what she was doing,
或许你能说说她当时没在做什么
maybe you can tell me what she wasn't doing.
副总统没有参加竞选活动捐赠者的早午餐会
The vice president was not at a brunch with campaign donors.
我会希望她没有
I would hope that she was not.
否则 我不确定现在我不会在我的权利范围内
Otherwise, I'm not sure if I wouldn't be within my rights
不展开一场空袭
not to launch a drone strike right now.
我被双重否定搞糊涂了 先生  什么?
I got lost in the double negative, sir. What?
我他妈的很生气
I'm fuckin' furious.
Jo蛋蛋!
Jonad!
是的 先生  去那家酒店
Yes, sir.  Get over to that hotel.
如果需要的话 用强硬的态度杠上副总统
Cut your face off and give it to the VP if you have to.
去让她对媒体说
Just get her to talk to the press.
说她不是那个挑战者
Say she is not the challenger.
我不会让你失望的 先生
I won't let you down, sir.
嘿  是的
Hey.  Yeah.
我真的很为那个派对兴奋
I'm really excited for that party.
我也是 我们会跳舞
I am, too. We'll dance.
我们会开始跳舞
We'll get our dance on.
一直跳
Dance on.
你们为什么这么紧张? 她非常冷静
Why are you guys so tense? She's completely chilled.
她他妈的完全不知道在干嘛
She's out of her fucking mind.
她会去我父母的40周年结婚纪念日
She's coming to my parents' 40th wedding anniversary.
是的 没错 Gary
Yeah, exactly, Gary.
她他妈的完全不知道在干嘛
She's out of her fucking mind.
嘿 女士 我取消了你的捐赠者早餐
Hey, ma'am. I cancelled the donor breakfast,
但我得跟他们坦白你撞破玻璃门的事情
but I did have to come clean about you walking through the glass door.
干得好 蠢货 现在每个人都会知道
Great job, ass hat. Now everyone's gonna know.
每个人都会知道她撞破了玻璃门 Dan
Everyone's gonna find out she walked through a glass door, Dan,
因为她看起来就像撞破了他妈的玻璃门
because she looks like she walked through a fucking glass door.
哦 看这个
Yeah, check this out.
他有什么问题?  我不知道
What's his problem?  I don't know.
过来这里 小姜饼
Get over here, gingerbread.
你知道吗? 你给她的贯叶连翘
You know what? That St. John's Wort that you gave her
和她的抗抑郁剂产生了反应
is reacting to her antidepressants.
你在说什么?
What are you talking about?
那是草本的 是来自大自然的
It's herbal. It's from the earth.
蘑菇也是 笨蛋  好吧 那是非法药物
So are mushrooms, dipshit.  Okay, that's illegal drugs.
摸摸这个 摸摸这个  枪?
feel this. feel this.  the guns?
天哪  嗷 嗷
Jesus.  Argh argh!
好了 嘿!  我会弄疼你
Okay. Hey!  I'll hurt ya.
喔 你的心情很好  我是
Wow, you're in a good mood.  I am.
你怎么样  一般 你知道?
How are you doing?  So-so, you know?
不太好 但是试着让一切平稳发展
Not great, but trying to keep things on an even keel.
嘿 你的那艘船怎么样了?
Hey, what about that boat of yours?
我卖不掉 没人想买它
I can't sell it. Nobody wants to buy her.
你想卖多少钱?
How much do you want for her?
诚实地说 为了摆脱那个该死的东西我会半价出售
Honestly, I would take half just to get rid of the damn thing.
我会按原价购买
I'll give you all of it.
您真的想买我的船?  没错
You really want to buy my boat?  Yeah.
握手 魔力Mikey
Shake on it, Magic Mikey.
您要买我的船?  是
You're gonna buy my boat?  I am.
恭喜  祝贺你
Congratulations!  Congratulations to you.
您刚得到了一艘船
You just got a boat.
我刚得到了一张选票  Mike!
And I just got a vote. Mike!
Mike 这儿需要你
Mike, you're needed in here.
我来了 我来了
I'm coming, I'm coming.
外面有他妈的媒体车了 Mike
There's fucking press vans outside, Mike.
你最好希望是因为Russell Crowe说要跳楼
You better hope Russell Crowe is threatening to jump.
好吧 我们得让她下楼露个面
All right, we're gonna have to get her downstairs for an appearance.
否则他们会开始乱猜
Otherwise, they're gonna start speculating.
听着 她现在是吃药吃高了
Look, she is fuckin' high right now.
是的 是的
Yeah, yeah.
你难道没注意到副总统过度兴奋了吗?
You didn't happen to notice that the veep is tripping balls?
Gary给了她一些会跟她吃的抗抑郁剂起反应的东西
Gary gave her something that is reacting with her antidepressants
把她变成了Julie Andrews (《音乐之声》女主角)
and turning her into Julie Andrews.
不 那没有
No, that's not doing it.
瞧 我们只需要让她呆在这 直到这个过去
lookWe just need to keep her here till this thing passes.
那我们给她洗胃怎么样?
What if we pump her stomach?
我以前洗过胃
I've had my stomach pumped before.
我想我能想出来怎么洗
I think I can figure it out.
敲敲 J大牛到了!  天
Knock, knock, J Rock o'clock!  Christ.
哦 有人订了激增服务?
Yeah, somebody ordered boom service?
作为一个高级白宫官员
As a senior White House official,
我要强行征用这里 Mike
I am commandeering this situation, Mike.
好吧 现在什么情况?
All right, what do you guys got for me?
哦 她刚刚撞破了一扇玻璃门
Okay, she just walked through a glass door,
结果有些讽刺地和某个未公开的首要事务撞了车
which is somewhat ironic building up to an invisible primary,
而她现在暂时因为服用混合镇定剂而有些疯癫
and she is temporarily insane on a cocktail of happy pills.
交给你了 船长
Over to you, Captain.
你刚破坏了他的大脑 Amy
You just broke his brain, Amy.
天 看那愚蠢的大张的嘴
Jesus, look at his stupid gaping mouth.
让我们扔点东西进去
Let's put stuff in it.
好吧 决定 听着
Okay, decision. Listen up.
副总统要发表声明
The veep will make a statement.
她要在摄像机前面发表这项声明
She will make this statement on camera
而且她得尽他妈的最快的速度
and she will make this statement
来发表声明
as soon as humanly fucking possible.
他妈的明白了吗(意大利语)?
Ca-fuckin' piche?
该死的你有什么问题 Andrew?
What in the hell is your problem, Andrew?
嗯?
What?
你为什么那么看着我?
What are you looking at me like that for?
你的...
Your...
哈?  你刚叫我Andrew
Huh?  You called me Andrew.
不 我没有
No, I did not.
我知道你是谁
I know who you are.
我甚至能用另一种方式叫你的名字...
I can even say your name the other way...
Hanoj
Hanoj.
好吧 理论上 Amy 你的第一步是什么?
All right, academically, Amy, what's your first move here?
Mike 去和媒体谈谈  没错 Mike 去和媒体谈谈
Mike, go talk to the press.  Yeah, Mike, go talk to the press.
我跟你一起  Gary 给她拿衣服
I'll tag team with you.  Gary, go get her some clothes.
没错 Gary 去给她拿些他妈的衣服 嗯?
Yeah, Gary, go get her some fucking clothes, huh?
嘿 是时候打扮和坦白了
Come on, it's time to dress up and fess up.
走 走 走
Go, go, go.
得说 我想我处理得挺好
Gotta say, I think I handled that pretty well.
大白天的时候呆在酒店里
There's something so sexy about being in a hotel
还蛮性感的 对吧?
in the middle of the day, right?
没错 四个人用一个马桶
Yep, four people to one toilet.
你能听到所有的水声
You can hear everything that hits the water.
你他妈的在哪? 摘棉花去织衣服么?
Where the fuck are you? Picking cotton to weave?
Amy 我找不到任何可以遮住她的东西
Amy, I can't find anything to cover her up.
她没有一件高领的衣服
She doesn't have any turtlenecks.
我已经把范围缩小到四套了
I've narrowed it down to four looks.
马上回来这里
Just get back here.
？？？Give me a number between one and four, please.
给我一到四当中的一个数 拜托
四  我想我更喜欢三
Four.  I think I prefer three.
那么去他的三  事实上 四不错
Fucking three, then.  Actually, four's good.
那么 谁会挑战这个总统?
So, who could challenge this president?
在此刻 我们听到的名字...
At the moment, the names we're hearing...
好吧 已经三个小时了
Okay, it has been three hours.
我需要她马上上电视
I need her on television now.
我需要给你画个线图吗 Jonah?
Do I need to draw you a line graph, Jonah?
多一点时间就少一点疯癫
More time equals less cuckoo.
我们需要让那些猜测迅速冷下来
We need to take a cold dump on the speculation.
她是那个会在两年后把帽子抛进决斗圈
Is she the mystery challenger who's going to throw her hat
的神秘挑战者吗?
into the ring to challenge POTUS in two years?
我们需要发消息称此圈内不允许丢帽子
We need to send the message that the ring is a hat-free zone.
不允许贝雷帽 不允许斯泰森毡帽(阔边高顶毡帽) 不允许小便帽
No berets, no Stetsons, no beanies...
你为什么要数帽子?
Why are you just listing hats?
Jonah是对的
Jonah's right.
我得去露露脸 我乱七八糟的脸
I've gotta put my face out there, my fucked-up face.
我感觉超好 这一觉我睡得很沉
I feel so good. I had such a deep sleep.
看上去我坐在这里就对了
Looks like I'll just be sitting over here being right.
哦 在和我们共事的700天里 你就对了一次
Yeah, in 700 days of working with us, you've been right once.
像个绅士一样坐着 可以吗?  哦 天哪
Sit like a gentleman, please?  Oh, my God.
你喜欢这个样子 Mike?
You like the view, Mike?
好吧 大家 副总统来了
Okay, everyone. The vice president.
副总统女士
Madam Vice President.
请给她些空间  你们好 你们好 伙计们
Please, give her some space.  Hi. Hi, guys.
很抱歉让你们久等了 我很好
I'm sorry for keeping you waiting. I'm fine.
我不希望你们认为我在隐瞒什么
I didn't want you to think I'm hiding anything.
因为那不是我的风格
'Cause that's not my style.
刚刚发生的就是我 呃...
What happened is that I, um...
我撞破了一扇玻璃门
I walked through a glass door.
唯一被重伤的是我的自尊
And the only thing that's really hurt is my pride.
是不是有什么突发状况?
Were there any mitigating circumstances?
是不是有在铺地毯或者...?
Was there carpeting or...?
那有在铺地毯吗 Mike?  是的
Was there carpeting there, Mike?  Yes.
那有 是的 被证实了
There was. Yes, it has been confirmed
那里有在铺地毯
that there was carpeting there.
您会参加明天的"动起来长跑" 对吗?
You will be doing the Get Moving Run tomorrow, correct?
我一定会跑的 (竞选)
I fully intend to run.
哦 不
Oh, no,
这他妈真是爆老子的痔疮
that's a fucking wire brush to my hemorrhoids.
谢谢 女士
Thank you, ma'am.
她要么就是疯了
So she's either crazy
要么就是开始了她的总统竞选活动
or she's starting a presidential campaign.
哦 我会说那两个是同义词
Yeah, I'd say the two are synonymous.
"我要竞选"?  不 不 不
"I intend to run"? No, no, no.
她是在说跑那个比赛 先生 那个一万米
She was talking about running the race, sir, the 10K.
搞定它 否则我会让你的卵蛋和桌子"联络"一下
Fix it or I'll liaise your balls to your desk.
是的 先生 感谢您持续的...
Yes, sir. And thank you for your continued...
他挂了
he's gone.
Amy Amy Amy 好吧 Amy
Amy, Amy, Amy. Okay, Amy.
她明天得去跑步
She needs to run tomorrow
将所有总统选举的猜测变走 好吗?
to magic away any presidential speculation, okay?
她不能跑那个趣味跑
She can't do the Fun Run.
这个时候她几乎不能走几步
She can barely do a convincing walk at the moment.
好吧 能并且会  不能而且不会
Okay, can and will.  Can't and won't.
马上上去然后蹂躏一只枕头
Now go up and screw a pillow.
房间已经付过钱了  哦
The room's paid for.  Oh.
趣味跑当天 早8:25
fun run day
这是刚从台湾来的
And this just in from Taiwan.
超棒  什么?
so Good.  What?
来这边  什么?
Come here.  What?
哦  搞什么啊?
Oh.  What the fuck?
你为什么笑?
Why are you laughing?
我喜欢卡通
I love cartoons.
天
Jesus.
那是你 Gary  闭嘴
That's you, Gary.  Shut up.
那个包一点都不像Leviathan
That doesn't even look like the Leviathan.
你还有什么消息?  外面还在说什么?
What else you got? Is there anything else out there?
您推迟与媒体的见面
Your delay in facing the press
引起了对您长期健康状况的猜测
has raised speculation on your long-term health.
什么?
What?
他们疑问您是否能胜任这份工作 女士
They're asking if you're up to the job, ma'am.
我是否胜任这份工作?
Am I up to the job?
哦 呀
Ooh, jeez.
哦  腿的问题?
Ooh.  the leg thing?
嗯  是的
Yeah.  Yeah.
说真的 我的能力完全超越了这份工作好么
Seriously, I am totally overqualified for this job.
停止!  你知道...
Stop it!  You know...
停止什么?  没什么
Stop What?  Nothing.
这些花是国防部长Maddox
These flowers came for you
送给你的
from the Secretary of Defense Maddox.
哦 看看
Oh, let's see.
Good luck with your Fun Run.		祝你在趣味跑上好运
别在起跑枪声鸣起的时候骂脏话
Try not to swear when the starter pistol goes off.
别这样  他就是个曲张的老二静脉
Come on.  He's just a varicose dick vein.
我没法忍受那个男人 好了 走吧 伙计们
I can't stand that guy. All right, let's go, guys.
我去了一家墨西哥卡拉OK餐馆
I went to a Mexican karaoke restaurant
唱了首Lenard Cohen的《哈利路亚》
and I did "Hallelujah" by Leonard Cohen.
哦 不 不是吧
Oh, no, you didn't.
我有 我把"哈利路亚"
I did, and I changed the "hallelujah"
to "jalape駉. "
改成了"墨西哥小辣椒"
哦 哈 哈! 我可以想象那有多好玩 先生
Oh ho ho! I can imagine that was very funny, sir.
哦 天哪 是委员会
Oh, Christ. It's the Committee.
他们会对总统调查投票
They're gonna vote on the POTUS investigation.
哦 我想会没事的 先生
Yeah, I think that's gonna be fine, sir.
哦 你当然会那么想 Jonah
Yeah, of course you do, Jonah.
你不懂里面的复杂性
You don't get the complexity.
你是这世界上最大的单细胞生物
You're the world's biggest single-cell organism.
嘿 Amy 你知道国务院的Schmidt吗?
Hey, Amy, you know Schmidt at the State Department?
他是那个告密者 没错
He's the whistleblower. Yeah.
总统会陷入大麻烦
POTUS is gonna be up Shit Creek
而我不会在他周围给他当他妈的踏板
and I am not hanging around to be his fucking paddle.
我不会  不会变成那样的 女士
I'm not.  It's not coming to that, ma'am.
我们不知道 我只是说
We don't know. All I'm saying is that
会有很艰难的选择要做 你明白吗?
there are going to be difficult choices to make, you know?
就像《苏菲的抉择》那么难的选择 (著名电影)
Like "Sophie's Choice" choices,
除了它更重要  因为会和我有关
except more important because it's gonna be about me.
哦 嘿 大家好!
Well, hey there!
好 很棒!
All right. Great!
好 女士  好了
All right, ma'am.  Okay.
她的妆真的太浓了
She is definitely wearing too much makeup.
她看起来就像Marcel Marceau (默剧小丑 "毕普先生")
She looks like Marcel Marceau.
没错 他也不能分辨真玻璃和空气的区别
Yeah. He couldn't tell the difference between real glass and air either.
别这样 这他妈的很有趣
Come on, that's fuckin' funny.
各就各位预备...  等等
on your marks...  Wait.
哦  我害怕
Yeah.  I'm scared.
...预备 跑!  耶 好
... get set, go!  Yeah. Okay.
哦 去  来吧!
Oh, shit.  Let's do it!
哦 我看到你了!
Yeah, I see you!
我看到你了
I see you.
一起动起来!
Let's get moving!
哦 天哪 我们有警告她
Oh, Christ. Did we warn her
其中一个动起来大使
one of the Get Moving ambassadors
是个只有一条腿的老兵吗?
was a one-legged veteran?
他就在她后面 她绝不会看到他
He's behind her. She's never gonna see him.
但等等 她那样打败一个一条腿的男人
But wait, does it look good...
看起来会好吗?
her beating a one-legged guy like that?
不 看起来不好
No, it doesn't look good.
另一个选择会更差 你不觉得吗?
The alternative is a little worse, don't you think?
关键是我们得让她看起来像是能打败那个男人
The key is we make it look like she could beat the guy,
但是她让他赢
but then she lets him win.
没错 用输换得的双赢 那不错
Yeah, a win-win by losing. That's good.
嗯?
Yeah?
喂?
Hello?
Gary 你得让她慢下来
Gary, you need to get her to slow down.
哦 谢天谢地
Oh, thank God.
如果她打败那个残疾人看起来会很糟
It looks bad if she's beating the disabled guy.
好吧
Okay.
嘿 女士 女士
Hey, ma'am, ma'am.
您得慢下来  为什么?
You gotta slow down.  Why?
看起来不怎么好
It looks bad.
哦 天 什么? 我的脸
Oh, God, what? My face.
不 您的脸看起来很好
No, your face looks fine.
您正在击败一个残疾人
You're beating a disabled guy.
哦 嘿 别对自己那么苛刻 Gary
Oh, come on. Don't be so hard on yourself, Gary.
哦 天 我阻止不了她 她不可阻止
Oh, God. I can't stop her. She's unstoppable.
Schmidt常务副国务卿正在作证
Dep Sec Schmidt is testifying.
众议院司法委员会
House Judiciary Committee
正在讨论弹劾投票
is discussing an impeachment vote.
把所有相关的东西都烧掉 包括这栋大楼
Burn everything incriminating, including this building.
烧掉所有白宫的宠物然后是你们自己
Burn all the White House pets and then yourselves.
先烧掉你们自己
Burn yourselves first.
Jonah 你下去赛跑场地
Jonah, you go down to the race site,
确保副总统说她会站在总统这边
make sure the vice president says she stands by POTUS.
Ryan先生 要确保副总统
Mr. Ryan, ensure that the vice president
不会回应任何关于弹劾投票的事情
does not respond to any questions about the impeachment vote.
那些是矛盾的命令
Those are contradictory orders.
你要确保她支持并驳斥回去
You make sure that she stands up and she shits back.
拒绝任何形式的参与  好吧 那么我应该...
Refuses to engage at all.  Okay, so I should...
他妈的选择一边  用你的判断力
Pick a fucking side.  Use your judgment.
先生 那不是我的强项
Sir, that's not my strongest suit.
哦 天
Aw, Christ.
国务院的Schmidt刚做了决定
Schmidt at the State Department just pushed the button.
司法委员会说他已经同意作证
The Judiciary Committee says he's agreed to testify.
哦 再帮我连上Gary
Okay, give me Gary again.
拜托 再次呼叫Gary  知道吗? 停在那边
Please, get me Gary again.  You know what? Pull over here.
这个会不会导致弹劾投票?
Could this go to an impeachment vote?
好吧 瞧 你们继续往前走
All right, look, you guys go ahead.
我们会去确保Gary跟上她  好的 好的
We're gonna make sure Gary keeps up with her. Okay, okay.
Gary! Gary 过来这!  Gary! Gary!
Gary! Gary, come here!  Gary! Gary!
她冲过终点线的时候
As soon as she crosses the finish line,
媒体会蜂拥而上围住她
the press is gonna be all over her.
好吧 那么我们说什么?  等等 等等
All right, so what do we say?  Hang on, hang on.
不 不 操 我们得走了  不 快来 伙计
No, no, fuck it. We gotta go.  No, come on, man.
快点!  操!
Come on!  Fuck!
Gary!
Gary
Gary.
什么? 什么?
What? What?
司法委员会正在谈论弹劾投票
The Judiciary Committee is talking impeachment vote.
我们需要给她一个回答
We need to give her a response.
我落后很多了
I'm way behind.
如果我继续说话 我会吐的
If I keep talking, I'm gonna vomit.
Jonah?
是的 怎么了 二逼Lorax(童话人物)?
Yeah. What's up, you fuckin' Lorax?
嘿 Dan 如果你正试着给副总统一个声明
Hey, Dan, if you're trying to get a statement to the veep,
是这个... 对总统全身心效忠 绝对的后盾
it's this... full commitment to the president, total backing.
不 不 不 不 她会支持他 但她不会做他的后盾
No, no, no, no. She will support him, but she will not back him.
他毒性太强了  不 绝对的后盾 完全的支持
He's too toxic.  No, full backing, full support.
哦 天 这拉链就像个干酪搓一样在磨我的老二
Oh, God, this zipper is like a cheese grater on my dick.
哈哈! Lorax
Ha ha! Lorax.
你觉得"巨人"Andre  Jagoff (法国摔跤手)
So which one of us do you think
会听我们两个谁的?
Andre the Giant Jagoff is gonna obey?
Jonah么?  没错
Jonah?  Yeah.
100块 听你的  真的?
100 bucks says you.  Really?
他是个蠢货
He's an idiot.
我很惊讶他能来工作 而不是被车撞或者被打脸
I'm surprised he gets to work without being hit by a car or punched in the mouth.
嗨!  抱歉
Hi!  Excuse me.
女士 Amy说 "我会在这个艰难的时刻
Ma'am, Amy says, "I give my support
给总统我的支持"
to the president in this very challenging time. "
强调尊重听证过程是很重要的
Emphasize it's important to respect the process of the hearing.
她需要明哲保身
She needs a get-out.
切入正题 Amy 我正被一根香蕉超过
Cut to the chase, Amy. I'm being overtaken by a banana.
我不能呼吸了 哦 我不能呼吸了
I can't breathe. Oh, I can't breathe.
女士 我需要您加速或者减速
Ma'am, I need you to speed up or slow down.
我们不能让您和香蕉出现在同一张照片上
We can't have you in a photo finish with a banana.
没错  抓拍比赛正待展开
Yeah.  It's a caption contest waiting to happen.
哦 我不能被一根香蕉打败
Yeah, I'm not gonna get beaten by a banana.
终点
finish
副总统女士! 副总统女士!
Madam Vice President! Madam Vice President!
？？？Well done.  Thank you.
干得好  谢谢
干得漂亮  谢谢
Nice job.  Thank you.
考虑到你的情况 结果不错 对吧?  是的
Not bad, considering, huh?  Yeah.
动起来的感觉很棒 伙计们
Feels good to get moving, guys.
哦 天 它让血液奔腾
Oh, my God, it gets the blood pumping.
你们要知道 健康生活方式...的关键
You know, the key really, folks, to a healthy lifestyle
是好好锻炼  呼!
is exercising well.  Hoo!
谢谢  对弹劾的谣言有什么想法吗?
Thank you.  Any comment on the impeachment rumors?
我 当然 已经说了所有
I, of course, have given my full account
我所知道的
of what I knew
而现在我确定
and now I'm sure
总统会做一样的事
the president will do the same.
？？？
那您会...
到此结束 到此结束
That's it, that's it.
？？？
副总统女士 我真的很想知道...
嘿 把手放到头顶
Come on, put your hands above your head.
把你的... 把它们抬起来
Put your... get them up.
过来 伙计 走吧
Come on, buddy. Let's go.
Mike 来吧  干得好 女士
Mike, come on.  Well done, ma'am.
我受够了
I am done.
唔 是的 女士 您跑完了
Mm-hmm. Yes, ma'am, you're all done.
我是说我受够了 我受够这一切了
I mean I am done. I am done with all of it.
副总统任期... 我是说忘记它吧
The vice presidency... I mean forget it.
说真的 Amy
Seriously, Amy.
你能预见到即将要发生什么 对吧?
You can see what's coming, can't you?
他会把我拖进所有的这些
He's gonna implicate me in all of this.
全部
All of it.
然后两年我都要站在这个
And then it's gonna be two years of standing
我憎恶的男人身边
next to this man that I loathe.
这是贯叶连翘影响下的话?
Is this just the St. John's Wort talking?
看我 我浑身都是疤
Look at me. I'm covered in scabs.
我闻起来就像流浪汉的肛门
I smell like a hobo's craphole.
忘了吧 忘了吧
Forget it. Forget it.
两年后我不会和他一起竞选
I'm not gonna run with him in two years.
我不会成为他的副总统
I'm not gonna be his vice president.
我结束了
I'm finished.
我会在六年后回来
I'll come back in six years
然后我会彻底拯救这个党派
and I'll save the party from itself.
嘿 你知道我用时多少吗 顺便问?
Hey, do you know what my time was, by the way?
呃 多少算不错?  8分钟一英里吧
Uh, what's good?  Like an eight-minute mile.
这样  嗯?
That.  Yeah?
哦 让我们动起来...
Yeah, let's get moving...
哦
Oh.
哦 天哪
Oh, my God.
那真残酷
That was really rough.
嘿 Mike
Hey, Mike,
我有些模糊的记忆
I have some sort of hazy memory
关于我承诺...要买...
of me promising to buy your...
你的船的事
your boat.
是的 您有 记得很准确
Yeah, you did. Well remembered.
那不会发生
That's not gonna happen.
你不可能相信我会做那个 对吧?
You can't hold me to that, right?
哦 不 当然 当然
Yeah, no. Sure. Of course.
嘿 那也太下作了
Man, that is low.
就像试着跟昏迷的人上床一样
That's like trying to have sex with somebody who's passed out.
嘿 女士 啊哼...
Hey, ma'am, ahem...
关于我父母的派对...
about my parents' party...
什么? 我以为你父母已经死了
What? I thought your parents were dead.
没有  没有?
No.  No?
没有 呃...
No. Um...
是他们四十周年结婚纪念日
It's their 40th wedding anniversary
您想来而我们打算去跳舞
and you wanted to come and we were gonna go dancing.
你知道的 那会是个大宴会
You know, it's gonna be a big blowout.
好吧 我是美利坚合众国的副总统
Okay, I'm the Vice President of the United States.
是的  你知道
Yeah.  You know.
我不可能跑去
I can't be running off to shindigs
我员工的父母组织的社交聚会
put on by the parents of people on my staff.
你知道我在说什么吗? 那太...
You know what I mean? That's completely...
哦 当然  ...荒唐 你明白吗?
Yeah, sure.  ... absurd, you know?
我是说 你从来没有...从来没有哪怕提到过你的父母
I mean, you've never... never even mentioned your parents before.
我就一直认为他们已经死了  哦
I've just always assumed that they were dead. great
我是说 我为什么不那么想呢?
I mean, why wouldn't I make that assumption?
您为什么不 对吗? 嗯 完全地 嗯
Why wouldn't you, right? Yeah, totally. Yeah.
让我们倒回去一会...
Let's get back for a second here...
你父母没死?  没
your parents are not dead?  No.
你也这么认为这真好笑
It's so funny that you thought that they were too.
我以为你是被收养的
I thought you were adopted.